<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tobias Grieger</title>
    <link>https://tbg.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tobias Grieger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 22:22:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tbg.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reading on the Energy Transition</title>
      <link>https://tbg.github.io/posts/reading-on-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 22:22:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbg.github.io/posts/reading-on-energy/</guid>
      <description>I was born a little over a year after the Chernobyl disaster and I grew up around stickers like these.
Nuclear energy is not very popular in Germany. It&amp;rsquo;s just normal to say it&amp;rsquo;s obviously bad and move on. Chernobyl, Fukushima, giant piles of nuclear waste polluting our planet for tens of thousand of years, what&amp;rsquo;s not to love.
For obvious reasons - the Gas and Climate sandwich crisis - I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to answer some obvious questions for myself: is this renewable transition actually realistic or are we just lying to ourselves?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I knew about the sharp nail and it got me anyway</title>
      <link>https://tbg.github.io/posts/incidental-complexity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 08:02:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbg.github.io/posts/incidental-complexity/</guid>
      <description>I spent the entirety of last morning dealing with the fallout of incorrectly handling a piece of largely unnecessary complexity in the CockroachDB code base. I was familiar with the complexity; I was around when the complexity was introduced many years ago; I field questions (by others working on CockroachDB) about it a few times a year; I was, yesterday morning, working specifically in an area touched by the complexity and in fact had just improved its code documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World Again</title>
      <link>https://tbg.github.io/posts/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 15:33:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbg.github.io/posts/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>Hello world, again Decided to given regular blogging a try again since I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed some of my friends and acquaintainces&amp;rsquo; newsletters and keep private notes anyway.
I have some ideas of what I might write about but I don&amp;rsquo;t want to scare anyone off :)
You can subscribe here and you will receive a non-annoying e-mail whenever there is something new to see here. Responses to that e-mail will reach me and will put a smile on my face.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
